Solley mss., 1888-2006 LMC 2885
Lilly Library
- Coachwork Catalogs
  - Germany
    - Glaserkarosserie G.M.B.H., "Wenn Cabriolet dann Glaser", 1936 (Box 18)
    - Glaserkarosserie G.M.B.H., "Glaser Karosserie Dresden"(SE: 4/C240), c. 1937 (Box 18)
    - Glaserkarosserie G.M.B.H., "1864 75 Jahre 1939..." (SE: 5/C241) (Box 18)
    - Glaserkarosserie G.M.B.H., Photographs (Box 18)
    - Karosserie Hagele, "Mercedes Station Wagon – Photographs, Plans", c. 1959 (Box 18)
    - Karosserie Hagele, Photographs (Box 18)
    - Alexis Kellner Berlin, "Alexis Kellner Berlin, N.W. 87"(SE: 1/C90), c. 1926 (Box 18)
    - Alexis Kellner Berlin, Photographs (Box 18)
    - Alexis Kellner Berlin, Misc. (Box 18)
    - Lehmann & Lindenheim, Misc. (Box 18)
    - Karrosserie Gebr. Ludewig, Essen, "Fur Sport und Reise...'Aero–Cabriolett'", c. 1931 (Box 18)
    - Jos. Neuss Berlin, "Jos. Neuss Berlin"(SE: 1/C31), c. 1910 (Box 18)
    - Spohn, Photographs (Box 18)
    - Stuttgarter Carosseriewerke Reutter & Co., "Original Reutter Carosserien", c. 1914 (Box 18)
    - Stuttgarter Carosseriewerke Reutter & Co., "Auch 1937 liefen wir..."(SE: 2/C242) (Box 18)
    - Benz, "1912 Benz"(pen and ink rendering by Josh Ferguson), 1949 (Apr. 29) (Box 35)
    - Rumpler, "1921/3 Car"(pen and ink rendering dated Dec. 1966) (Box 35)
  - Great Britain
    - E.D. Abbot Ltd., "Drop Head Foursome"(SE: 1/C243), 1934-1935 (Box 18)
    - E.D. Abbot Ltd., "Rolls–Royce and Bentley Coachwork", 1951 (Box 18)
    - E.D. Abbot Ltd., "Rolls–Royce and Bentley Coachwork", 1953 (Box 18)
    - E.D. Abbot Ltd., Photographs (Box 18)
    - E.D. Abbot Ltd., Misc. (Box 18)
    - Jack Barclay Ltd., "The Pre–Eminence of Barclay..."(SE: 2/C245), 1939 (Box 18)
    - Jack Barclay Ltd., "Examples of Barclay...Phantom III"(SE: 3/C246) (photocopy), 1938–1939 (Box 18)
    - Jack Barclay Ltd., "Examples of Barclay..."(SE: 3/C247), 1938–1939 (Box 18)
    - Jack Barclay Ltd., "Special Coachwork by James Young...", 1946–1947 (Box 18)
    - Jack Barclay Ltd., "Rolls Royce", c. 1951 (Box 18)
    - Jack Barclay Ltd., "Largest Official Retailers...", 1952 (May) (Box 18)
    - Jack Barclay Ltd., Photographs (Box 18)
    - Barker & Co. (Coachbuilders) Ltd., "Barker & Co....Over 200 Years"(SE: 1/C34), 1910–1911 (Box 18)
    - Barker & Co. (Coachbuilders) Ltd., "Barker & Co."(SE: 2/C35), 1912–1913 (Box 18)
    - Barker & Co. (Coachbuilders) Ltd., "Barker & Co."(SE: 3/C91), 1922–1923 (Box 18)
    - Barker & Co. (Coachbuilders) Ltd., "Barker Coachwork...20–H.P. Rolls–Royce..."(SE: 4/C92), c. 1926 (Box 18)
    - Barker & Co. (Coachbuilders) Ltd., "Barker Coachwork"(SE: 5/C163), 1928 (Box 18)
    - Barker & Co. (Coachbuilders) Ltd., "Coachbuilding 1932–1933"(SE: 8/C248) (Box 18)
    - Barker & Co. (Coachbuilders) Ltd., "Coachbuilding 1933–1934"(SE: 9/C249) (Box 18)
    - Barker & Co. (Coachbuilders) Ltd., "Coachbuilding 1936–1937"(SE: 10/C250) (Box 18)
    - Barker & Co. (Coachbuilders) Ltd., "Coachbuilding 1937–1938"(SE: 11/C251) (Box 18)
    - Barker & Co. (Coachbuilders) Ltd., Photographs, (2 folders) (Box 18)
    - Barker & Co. (Coachbuilders) Ltd., Misc. (Box 18)
    - Bertelli, Photographs (Box 19)
    - Blake, Photographs (Box 19)
    - Caffyn's Ltd., "Rolls–Royce Coachwork..."(SE: 1/C93), 1925–1926 (Box 19)
    - Calshot, "Calshot"(SE: 1/C167), c. 1932 (Box 19)
    - Carlton Carriage Co. Ltd., "Carlton Coachwork"(SE: 1/C168), 1927–1928 (Box 19)
    - Carlton Carriage Co. Ltd., "Carlton Coachwork"(SE: 2/C253), 1935–1936 (Box 19)
    - Carlton Carriage Co. Ltd., "Carlton Coachwork"(SE: 3/C254), 1937 (Box 19)
    - Carlton Carriage Co. Ltd., Photographs (Box 19)
    - Charlesworth, "Charlesworth Bodies Ltd...."(SE: 1/C36), 1914 (Box 19)
    - Coachcraft Ltd., "Hudson's 'Sports' Saloon...", 1935 (Box 19)
    - Joseph Cockshoot, "Joseph Cockshoot and Company Ltd."(SE: 1/C94), 1924–1925 (Box 19)
    - Connaught, "Connaught Motor & Carriage Co. Ltd."(SE: 1/C37), 1909 (Box 19)
    - Connaught, "Connaught"(SE: 3/C169), c. 1927 (Box 19)
    - Corsica, Photographs (Box 19)
    - Corscia, Misc. (Box 19)
    - Cunningham, Photographs (Box 19)
    - Charles Follett Ltd., "Inspired Coachwork..."(photocopy), 1936 (Box 19)
    - Freestone & Webb, "'Rolls–Royce 'Silver Wraith' Chassis' Design No. 3171", 1957 (Box 19)
    - Freestone & Webb, "Rolls–Royce Silver Cloud...Limousine – Design No. 3194/a", c. 1950s (Box 19)
    - Freestone & Webb, "Silver Cloud Chassis – Design No. 3206", c. 1950s (Box 19)
    - Freestone & Webb, Photographs (Box 19)
    - Freestone & Webb, Misc. (Box 19)
    - Grovesnor, Photographs (Box 19)
    - Holbrook, Photographs (Box 19)
    - Hooper & Co., "'Hooper' Motor Bodies"(SE: 1/C39) (facsimile), 1914 (Box 19)
    - Hooper & Co., "Hooper Motor Carriages"(SE: 2/C97), 1921 (Box 19)
    - Hooper & Co., "Hooper Special Coachwork Features"(1988 reprint), c. 1927 (Box 19)
    - Hooper & Co., "Hooper"(SE: 5/C174), 1927–1928 (Box 19)
    - Hooper & Co., "Daimler Hooper"(SE: 6/C175), c. 1928 (Box 19)
    - Hooper & Co., "Through Eight Reigns"(SE: 8/C257), 1937 (Box 19)
    - Hooper & Co., "Hooper Limousine, Rolls-Royce Silver Wraith, No. 8195", 1948–1949 (Box 19)
    - Hooper & Co., "Specification Design No. 8400 – Rolls-Royce...", 1955 (Nov. 15) (Box 19)
    - Hooper & Co., "Specification Design No. 8500 – Rolls-Royce Silver Wraith", 1957-1958 (Box 19)
    - Hooper & Co., "Specification No. 185 – Fixed Head Couple–Daimler", c. 1956 (Box 19)
    - Hooper & Co., "Price List", 1955 (Nov. 15) (Box 19)
    - Hooper & Co., Photographs (Box 19)
    - Hooper & Co., Misc. (Box 19)
    - Maltby, "The Redfern Saloon Tourer", 1937 (Box 19)
    - Mann Egerton, "Mann Egerton Co.", 1914 (Box 19)
    - Mann Egerton, "Coachwork at Olympia"(SE: 1/C178), c. 1932 (Box 19)
    - Mann Egerton, "Distinctive Coachwork...Rolls–Royce Phantom III"(SE: 4/C261), 1936–1937 (Box 19)
    - Maythorn & Son, "Maythorn's Coach–Built Motor Bodies"(SE: 1/C40), c. 1912 (Box 19)
    - Maythorn & Son, Photographs (Box 19)
    - Melhuish, Photographs (Box 19)
    - Arthur Mulliner (Northampton) Ltd., "A. Mulliner...Coachcraft"(SE: 1/C179), 1929 (Box 19)
    - Arthur Mulliner (Northampton) Ltd., "Arthur Mulliner Limited"(SE: 2/C180), 1931 (Box 19)
    - H.J. Mulliner & Co. Ltd., "Touring Limousine", 1955 (Box 19)
    - H.J. Mulliner & Co. Ltd., "Special Coachwork...Silver Wraith Chassis, Design 7356", 1957 (Box 19)
    - H.J. Mulliner & Co. Ltd., "Convertible Drophead Coupe...Silver Cloud Chassis", 1956 (Box 19)
    - H.J. Mulliner & Co. Ltd., "Specification Silver Cloud Drophead Coupe – Drawing No. 7410", c. 1956 (Box 19)
    - H.J. Mulliner & Co. Ltd., "Specification Drawing. No. 7410 – Silver Cloud Drophead Coupe", 1956 (Box 19)
    - H.J. Mulliner & Co. Ltd., "Specification Drawing 7409 – Silver Cloud", c. 1956 (Box 19)
    - H.J. Mulliner & Co. Ltd., "Special Coachwork...Bentley S. Chassis...Silver Cloud", c. 1957 (Box 19)
    - H.J. Mulliner & Co. Ltd., "25/30 Rolls–Royce 'E' – Drawing No. 6066", 1937 (Box 19)
    - H.J. Mulliner & Co. Ltd., "Bentley...Saloon – Drawing No. 7220", 1952 (Box 19)
    - H.J. Mulliner & Co. Ltd., "Bentley...Drophead Coupe – Drawing No. 7259", 1952–1953 (Box 19)
    - H.J. Mulliner & Co. Ltd., "Specification Design 7400 – Bentley Continental", 1956 (Box 19)
    - H.J. Mulliner & Co. Ltd., "Flying Spur...", c. 1957 (Box 19)
    - H.J. Mulliner & Co. Ltd., "Two Door Sports Saloon…Bentley...", c. 1950s (Box 19)
    - H.J. Mulliner & Co. Ltd., "Specification Design No. 7500 – Bentley Continental…", c. 1957 (Box 19)
    - H.J. Mulliner & Co. Ltd., "Bentley Continental – Two Door Saloon", c. 1960s (Box 19)
    - H.J. Mulliner & Co. Ltd., Photographs (Box 19)
    - H.J. Mulliner & Co. Ltd., Misc. (Box 19)
    - H.J. Mulliner & Harold Radford, "The 'Safari' Car", c. 1950s (Box 19)
    - H.R. Owen (Gurney Nutting), "Coachwork for Rolls–Royce by h. r. Owen Ltd."(SE: 1/C263), 1932–1933 (Box 19)
    - H.R. Owen (Gurney Nutting), "Owen Body Designs...Rolls–Royce and Bentley"(SE: 2/C264), 1935 (Box 19)
    - H.R. Owen (Gurney Nutting), "Copyright Designs – Rolls–Royce and Bentley"(SE: 4/C266), 1939 (Box 19)
    - H.R. Owen (Gurney Nutting), Photographs (Box 19)
    - H.R. Owen (Gurney Nutting), Renderings (Box 19)
    - H.R. Owen (Gurney Nutting), Misc. (Box 19)
    - Park Ward, "An Album of Park Ward Coachwork"(SE: 2/C181), c. 1930 (Box 19)
    - Park Ward, " An Album of Park Ward Coachwork"(SE: 3/268) (facsimile), 1933-1934 (Box 19)
    - Park Ward, "An Album of Park Ward Coachwork"(SE: 4/C269), 1934-1935 (Box 19)
    - Park Ward, "An Album of Park Ward Coachwork"(SE: 6/C271), 1937 (Box 19)
    - Park Ward, "Blueprint – 25–30 H.P. Rolls–Royce – Drawing No. 12692", 1937 (Box 19)
    - Park Ward, "Enclosed Limousine – Rolls–Royce Silver Wraith Chassis – Drawing No. 51", c. 1930s (Box 19)
    - Park Ward, "Specification – Design No. 702 – Rolls–Royce Silver Wraith", c. 1957 (Box 19)
    - Park Ward, "Rolls–Royce 'Silver Wraith' – Design No. 704...", c. 1950s (Box 19)
    - Park Ward, "Specification – Design No. 705 – Rolls–Royce 'Silver Wraith'", c. 1957 (Box 19)
    - Park Ward, "Specification for Park Ward Coachwork – Bentley Chassis – Design No. 147", 1950–1951 (Box 19)
    - Park Ward, "Specification – Design No. 700 – Bentley...", c. 1957 (Box 19)
    - Park Ward, "Specification – Design No. 872 – Bentley...", c. 1957 (Box 19)
    - Park Ward, Photographs (Box 19)
    - Park Ward, Misc. (Box 19)
    - Harold Radford & Co., "HR Introducing 'The Countryman'...", 1949 (Box 20)
    - Harold Radford & Co., "HR 'The Countryman' Mark II...", 1952 (Box 20)
    - Harold Radford & Co., "The Countryman Mark II...", 1953 (Box 20)
    - Harold Radford & Co., "Coachwork by Harold Radford – Silver Dawn", c. 1950s (Box 20)
    - Harold Radford & Co., "The Countryman Mark III...", 1954 (Box 20)
    - Harold Radford & Co., "Rolls–Royce 'Silver Cloud' – Bentley 'S' Series…", 1956–1957 (Box 20)
    - Harold Radford & Co., "Rolls–Royce 'Silver Cloud' II – Bentley 'S'...", 1960 (Box 20)
    - Harold Radford & Co., "Rolls–Royce ' Silver Cloud' III – Bentley 'S'...", 1962 (Box 20)
    - Harold Radford & Co., Misc. (Box 20)
    - Rippon, Photographs (Box 20)
    - Salmons & Sons, "Tickford Sunshine Coachwork"(SE: 3/C275), 1933–1934 (Box 20)
    - Salmons & Sons, "Tickford"(SE: 5/C277), 1935 (Box 20)
    - Salmons & Sons, Misc. (Box 20)
    - Southern Motor Co., "Rolls Royce Cars"(SE: 1/C279), 1939 (Box 20)
    - Southern Motor Co., Photographs (Box 20)
    - Surbico, Photographs (Box 20)
    - Thrupp & Maberly Ltd., "Some Designs for 1928"(SE: 2/C185) (Box 20)
    - Thrupp & Maberly Ltd., "A Little Book of Coachwork Photographs"(SE: 4/C188), 1931 (Box 20)
    - Thrupp & Maberly Ltd., "The Finest English Coachwork"(SE: 6/C280), 1933 (Box 20)
    - Thrupp & Maberly Ltd., "The Finest English Coachwork"(SE: 7/C281), 1935 (Box 20)
    - Thrupp & Maberly Ltd., "T & M"(SE: 8/C282), 1936 (Box 20)
    - Thrupp & Maberly Ltd., "Thrupp & Maberly Ltd."(SE: 9/C283), 1936 (Box 20)
    - Thrupp & Maberly Ltd., "Rolls–Royce PIII Drop–Head Sedanca No. 1060/A...", 1936 (Box 20)
    - Thrupp & Maberly Ltd., Photographs (Box 20)
    - Thrupp & Maberly Ltd., Misc. (Box 20)
    - Vanden Plas (England) 1923 Ltd., "Vanden Plas"(SE: 1/C189), c. 1928 (Box 20)
    - Vanden Plas (England) 1923 Ltd., "Phantom III – Rolls–Royce Continental – Blueprint Design 13797", c. 1935 (Box 20)
    - Vanden Plas (England) 1923 Ltd., "Vanden Plas Princess 1100", 1965 (Box 20)
    - Vanden Plas (England) 1923 Ltd., Photographs (Box 20)
    - Vanden Plas (England) 1923 Ltd., Misc. (Box 20)
    - Vincents of Reading, "Coachwork by Vincents of Reading"(SE: 2/C285), 1933 (Box 20)
    - Vincents of Reading, "Elegant Bodies for the World's Finest..."(SE: 3/C286), 1933 (Box 20)
    - Vincents of Reading, "Exclusive Coachwork by Vincents of Reading"(SE: 4/C287), 1935 (Box 20)
    - Weymann, "The Hall Mark of Comfort"(SE: 1/C191), 1929–1930 (Box 20)
    - Weymann, Misc. (Box 20)
    - Windovers Ltd., "Motor Bodies Windovers, Ltd."(SE: 1/C41), 1912 (Box 20)
    - Windovers Ltd., "Windovers"(SE: 3/C288), 1933 (Box 20)
    - Windovers Ltd., "Coachwork of Quality"(SE: 4/C289), 1934–1935 (Box 20)
    - Windovers Ltd., "Distinctive Coachwork"(SE: 5/C290), 1936 (Box 20)
    - Windovers Ltd., "Windovers"(SE: 6/C291), 1937 (Box 20)
    - Windovers Ltd., "Windovers"(SE: 7/C292), 1938 (Box 20)
    - Windovers Ltd., "Rolls–Royce 25/30 HP – Design No. 4992", 1937 (Box 20)
    - Windovers Ltd., "Windover Enclosed Limousine...'Silver Wraith' Chassis", 1946–1947 (Box 20)
    - Windovers Ltd., "Windover Saloon...Bentley Mark VI 4¼ Litre Chassis", 1946–1947 (Box 20)
    - Windovers Ltd., Photographs (Box 20)
    - Windovers Ltd., Misc. (Box 20)
    - Wylder, "Modern Designs of Wylder Coachwork"(SE: 1/C192), 1932 (Box 20)
    - James Young Ltd., "Specification Design No. WRM 30 – Silver Wraith", 1953–1954 (Box 20)
    - James Young Ltd., "Specification Design No. C20 SD – Silver Dawn", 1953–1954 (Box 20)
    - James Young Ltd., "Specification Design No. C20 – Bentley", 1953–1954 (Box 20)
    - James Young Ltd., "Specification Design No. WRM 31 (Silver Wraith)", c. 1957 (Box 20)
    - James Young Ltd., "Specification Design No. CT 29 H. R. Owen (Bentley)", c. 1950s (Box 20)
    - James Young Ltd., "Specification Design No. CT 30 (Bentley)", c. 1950s (Box 20)
    - James Young Ltd., "Rolls Royce", c. 1960 (Box 20)
    - James Young Ltd., "James Young Limited Centenary Year", 1963 (Box 20)
    - James Young Ltd., "Specification Design No. P.V. 15 S.D. (Phantom V)", 1965 (Box 20)
    - James Young Ltd., "Specification of...Rolls–Royce 'Silver Shadow'...", 1966 (Box 20)
    - James Young Ltd., "Maintenance Instructions", n.d. (Box 20)
    - James Young Ltd., Photographs (Box 20)
    - James Young Ltd., Misc. (Box 20)
  - Holland
    - Alexis Kellner, "Alexis Kellner Hoflieferant..." (SE: 1/C193), c. 1931 (Box 20)
    - Pennock, "Pennock Coachbuilders The Hague", c. 1950 (Box 20)
    - Van Koppen, "Van Koppen Carrosserie Fabriek", c. 1950s (Box 20)
  - Italy
    - Balbo, "Carrozzeria Succ. Balbo", c. 1950 (Box 20)
    - Balbo, "Carrozzera Succ. Balbo", c. 1950 (Box 20)
    - Bertone, Photographs (Box 20)
    - Bertone, Misc. (Box 20)
    - Castagna, "Carrozzerria Castagna"(SE: 1/C196), 1927 (Box 20)
    - Castagna, "Castagna"(SE: 2/C197), 1927; (14 photographic renderings) (Box 20)
    - Castagna, Photographs (Box 20)
    - E. Garavini, "Carrozzeria E. Garavini & C. Torino"(SE: 1/C198), c. 1930 (Box 20)
    - E. Garavini, Misc. (Box 20)
    - Ghia, Photographs (Box 20)
    - Ghia, Misc. (Box 20)
    - Carrozzeria Imperia, "Carrozzeria Imperia Societa Anonima", c. 1925 (Box 20)
    - Pinin Farina, "Two Photographs – 1948 Bentley Berlina 5 – 1949 Bentley Cabriolet 2", 1948–1949 (Box 20)
    - Pinin Farina, "Bentley T Series – Specifications and Photograph", 1968 (Box 20)
    - Pinin Farina, Photographs (Box 20)
    - Pinin Farina, Misc. (Box 20)
    - Sala, "Isotta Models – 4 Numbered Photographs", 1927–1928 (Box 20)
    - Sala, Photographs (Box 20)
    - Touring, "Carrozzeria Touring"(SE: 1/C199), c. 1932 (Box 20)
    - Touring, Photographs (Box 20)
    - Touring, Misc. (Box 20)
    - Vignale, Misc. (Box 20)
  - Poland
    - Jelcz Coachworks, Misc. (Box 20)
  - Sweden
    - Scania – Vabis, Photographs (Box 20)
  - Switzerland
    - Aktiengesellschaft fur Verkehrspatente, "Der Echte Stromlinienwagen", 1934–1935 (Box 20)
    - Beutler, Photographs (Box 20)
    - F. Brichet, "Carrosserie Automobile F. Brichet Geneve"(SE: 1/C104) (photocopy), 1925–1926 (Box 20)
    - F. Brichet, "La Granciel de F. Brichet", c. 1928 (Box 20)
    - Graber, "Schweizer Karosserie 'Graber'", c. 1948 (Box 20)
    - Graber, Photographs (Box 20)
    - Graber, Misc. (Box 20)
    - Walter Kong, Photographs (Box 20)
    - Walter Kong, Misc. (Box 20)
    - Reinbolt & Christie A.G., "Der MG 'Zwei–Liter' Tourenwagen"(SE: 1/C298), c. 1937 (Box 20)
    - Reinbolt & Christie A.G., "Das feine ...2, 6 lt. Chassis..."(SE: 2/C299), 1939 (Box 20)
    - Reinbolt & Christie A.G., Photographs (Box 20)
    - Gebr. Tuscher & Co., "Jaguar Cabriolet"(SE: 1/C300) (photocopy), 1938–1939 (Box 20)
    - Carrosserie Worblaufen, "Carrosserie Worblaufen..."(SE: 1/C301), 1936 (Box 20)
    - Carrosserie Worblaufen, "Carrosserie Worblaufen Fr. Ramseier..."(SE: 3/C303), c. 1938 (Box 20)
    - Carrosserie Worblaufen, "Carrosserie Worblaufen", c. 1947 (Box 20)
    - Carrosserie Worblaufen, "Carrosserie Worblaufen", c. 1948 (Box 20)
    - Carrosserie Worblaufen, Photographs (Box 20)
    - Carrosserie Worblaufen, Misc. (Box 20)
  - United States
    - Anthony, "Anthony Custom Built Carriages"(SE: 1/C105), 1912 (Box 21)
    - Babcock, Misc. (Box 21)
    - Bender, Robinson Co., Inc, "Bender, Robinson..."(SE: 1/C106) (photocopy), 1916–1917 (Box 21)
    - Bender, Robinson Co., Inc, Photographs (Box 21)
    - Bohman & Schwartz, Photographs (Box 21)
    - Bohman & Schwartz, Misc. (Box 21)
    - Brewster & Co., "A New Town Car..."(SE: 5/C304), 1934 (Box 21)
    - Brewster & Co., "A New Town Car..."(SE: 6/C305), 1935 (Box 21)
    - Brewster & Co., Photographs (Box 21)
    - Brewster & Co., Misc. (Box 21)
    - Brunn Co., "Brunn & Co."(SE: 2/C108) (photocopy), 1923–1924 (Box 21)
    - Brunn Co., "Individual Custom Built Bodies..."(SE: 5/C201), 1932 (Box 21)
    - Brunn Co., "Prepared for Mr. A. C. Hickmott..."(SE: 8/C308), 1938 (Box 21)
    - Brunn Co., Photographs (Box 21)
    - Brunn Co., Misc. (Box 21)
    - Derham Body Co., "Photographs and Renderings – Isotta, Minerva, etc.", c. 1930 (Box 21)
    - Derham Body Co., "Derham Bodies"(SE: 1/C309), c. 1935 (Box 21)
    - Derham Body Co., "The Derham Story...", 1967 (Box 21)
    - Derham Body Co., Photographs (Box 21)
    - Derham Body Co., Misc. (Box 21)
    - Dietrich Inc., "23 Plates of Coachwork – Lincoln, Packard, Chrysler", 1928–1930 (Box 21)
    - Dietrich Inc., Photographs (Box 21)
    - Dietrich Inc., Misc. (Box 21)
    - Don Lee, "Custom Motor Coaches..."(SE: 1/C111) (photocopy), 1920-1921 (Box 21)
    - Fleetwood, "Fleetwood"(SE: 1/C43), c. 1915 (Box 21)
    - Fleetwood, "Fleetwood Metal Body Company"(photocopy), c. 1917 (Box 21)
    - Fleetwood, "Fleetwood Metal Body Company"(photocopy), c. 1920 (Box 21)
    - Fleetwood, "Fleetwood Custom Coachwork…Cadillac"(SE: 7/C207), 1929 (Box 21)
    - Fleetwood, "The Book of Fleetwood"(SE: 11/C211), 1932 (Box 21)
    - Fleetwood, "The Book of Fleetwood"(SE: 12/C310), 1933 (Box 21)
    - Fleetwood, Misc. (Box 21)
    - Graff, "Graff Motor Coachwork"(SE: 1/C115) (photocopy), c. 1921 (Box 21)
    - Holbrook, "Holbrook, Hudson, N.Y."(SE: 2/C117) (photocopy), c. 1923 (Box 21)
    - Holbrook, Misc. (Box 21)
    - J.B. Judkins Company, "Photographs – Packard, Stearns–Knight, Pierce Arrow", c. 1925, 1927, 1928 (Box 21)
    - J.B. Judkins Company, "Judkins Where Fine Coachwork..."(SE: 2/C213), c. 1930 (Box 21)
    - J.B. Judkins Company, "Judkins Where Fine Coachwork..."(SE: 3/C316), c. 1936 (Box 21)
    - J.B. Judkins Company, Misc. (Box 21)
    - Larkins, Misc. (Box 21)
    - LeBaron, "LeBaron"(SE: 2/C215), 1928 (Box 21)
    - LeBaron, "LeBaron"(SE: 4/C217), 1930–1931 (Box 21)
    - LeBaron, "Renderings – Packard 845 Convertible Roadster", 1931 (Box 21)
    - LeBaron, Photographs (Box 21)
    - LeBaron, Misc. (Box 21)
    - Locke, "Locke"(SE: 1/C118a), 1926 (Box 21)
    - Locke, Misc. (Box 21)
    - Merrimac Body Co., Photographs (Box 21)
    - Murphy, "2 Photographs – Packard Collapsible Sedan", c. 1929 (Box 21)
    - Murphy, Photographs (Box 21)
    - Murphy, Misc. (Box 21)
    - Palmer & Singer, Catalogs of the Palmer & Singer Manufacturing..."(photocopy), c. 1910 (Box 21)
    - J.M. Quinby & Co., "Aluminum Automobile Bodies..."(SE: 1/C45), 1905 (Box 21)
    - J.M. Quinby & Co., "J. M. Quinby & Co. Builders..."(SE: 2/C46), c. 1906 (Box 21)
    - J.M. Quinby & Co., Misc. (Box 21)
    - Rollston, "Photographs by John Adams Davis – Minerva, Packard", c. 1929–1930 (Box 21)
    - Rollston, Photographs (Box 21)
    - Rollston, Misc. (Box 21)
    - Rubay Carrosserie Automobile, "Rubay Carrosserie Automobile"(SE: 1/C119), 1919–1920 (Box 21)
    - Rubay Carrosserie Automobile, "Rubay Carrosserie for Packard Twin Six"(SE: 2/C120) (photocopy), 1919 (Box 21)
    - Schutte, Misc. (Box 21)
    - Springfield Metal Body Co., "Springfield Metal Body Co....Aluminum Bodies"(SE: 1/C47), 1905 (Box 21)
    - Springfield Metal Body Co., "Automobile Bodies and Tops"(SE: 2/C48), 1911 (Box 21)
    - Waterhouse, "Packard 845 Convertible Victoria – Rendering No. 4415", 1931 (Box 21)
    - Waterhouse, Misc. (Box 21)
    - Weymann, "Weymann Bodies"(SE: 2/C222), c. 1930 (Box 21)
    - Willoughby, "Custom Bodies Created by Willoughby", 1932 (Box 21)
    - Willoughby, Renderings (Box 21)
    - Willoughby, Misc. (Box 21)
    - Automobile Shows, "New York Automobile Show – Descriptive Catalog", 1919 (Feb. 1–15) (Box 21)
    - Automobile Shows, "Automobile Salon – Hotel Commodore – New York – Souvenir Catalogue", 1922 (Box 21)
    - Automobile Shows, "Automobile Salon – New York – Souvenir Catalogue", 1927 (Box 21)
    - Automobile Shows, "Automobile Salon – Chicago – Souvenir Catalogue", 1929 (Box 21)
    - Automobile Shows, "Automobile Salon – New York – Souvenir Catalogue", 1930 (Box 21)
    - Automobile Shows, Misc. (Box 21)
- Miscellaneous
  - The Awakening, c. 1913 (Box 21)
  - Super Ace Discs, c. 1930 (Box 21)
  - Aus Bois de Boulougne...27 Juin 1930 Grand Concours d'elegance feminine en automobile (Box 21)
  - Concours d'elegance feminine en automobile..., 1934 (Box 21)
  - Lucas Dynamo Lighting System, 1914 (Box 21)
  - Solley Automobile Catalogue Inventory (draft), (2 folders) (Box 22)
  - Page proofs, etc. for Solley's Book Prestige, Status and Works of Art (Box 22)
  - Photographs (automobiles) – Negatives, Proof Sheets (misc.) (Box 22)
  - Photographs – Unidentified, Misc. (Box 22)
  - Photographs – Charles K. Bower & Sons Proof Sheets – Coachbuilders (Box 22)
  - Renderings – Ink and Watercolor – Cadillac, unidentified (Box 22)
  - The Ten Best Motoring Books (Peter Richley), n.d. (Box 22)
  - Automobile Races, Rallys, and Tours (Misc.) (Box 22)
  - Automobile Collections and Collectors (Box 22)
  - Automobile Parts and Accessories (Box 22)
  - Automobile Shows, Althorp Park – List of Entries, 1993, 1996 (Box 22)
  - Automobile Shows, Antique Auto Show – "71st Regiment Armory – New York", 1945 (Mar. 8–14) (Box 22)
  - Automobile Shows, Automobiles Classiques – Louis Vuitton – Bagatelle, 1990 (Sept. 8–9) (Box 22)
  - Automobile Shows, Automobiles Classiques – Louis Vuitton – Bagatelle, 1992 (Sept. 12–13) (Box 22)
  - Automobile Shows, Automobiles Classiques – Louis Vuitton – Bagatelle, 1993 (Sept. 11–12) (Box 22)
  - Automobile Shows, Automobiles Classiques – Louis Vuitton – Bagatelle, 1994 (Sept. 10–11) (Box 22)
  - Automobile Shows, Automobiles Classiques – Louis Vuitton – Bagatelle, 1995 (Sept. 9–10) (Box 22)
  - Automobile Shows, Concours d'Elegance – Louis Vuitton – Stowe, Buckingham, 1990 (July 28) (Box 22)
  - Automobile Shows, Concours d'Elegance – 39th Annual – Pebble Beach, 1989 (Aug. 20) (Box 22)
  - Automobile Shows, Concours d'Elegance – 40th Annual – Pebble Beach, 1990 (Aug. 19) (Box 22)
  - Automobile Shows, Louis Vuitton Classic – 10th Anniversary, 1999 (June 5) (Box 22)
  - Automobile Shows (Misc.) (Box 22)
  - Motor Carriage Body Designs, 1907 (Box 22)
  - General Motors – Customer Research Ballot, c. 1930s (Box 22)
  - Prices of 1939 Cars (Box 22)
  - Automobile Companies and Cars (Misc.) (Box 22)
  - Automobile Coachwork Companies (Misc.) (Box 22)
  - Automobiles (Misc. and Unidentified) (Box 22)
  - Automobile Auction and Dealer Catalogues and Advertisements (Box 22)
  - Automobiles – Notable Automobiles and Owners (Box 22)
  - Correspondence (Box 22)
  - The Arrow – Series 86 – Model 4, 1986 (Box 23)